We do all the recruitment digitally.
99.99% of the people join us from all over India
and right now the 250 people who are already
associated with us in Lombard, all of them are
connected digitally, some from Assam, some from
Punjab, some from Maharashtra, some from UP, some
from Delhi, people from everywhere are associated with us
and no one faces a single
challenge because the company is running since 2001
and not just from today, but since 2001, it
is a digitally sound proof company, it
works brilliantly, its apps are so amazing,
its digital working is so
great that there is no need to go to any branch.
[Music]
Hello, how are you guys, today
we are going to do something very special and wonderful.
Today Ajay Kumar ji is sitting with me
from ICC Lombard and
he is very welcome to our studio today. There are
many such doubts, people who
want to join ICC Lombard,
want to know about ICC Lombard, what are the
good things in ICC Lombard,
what kind of process is there, how do we help you
people  You can generate a next level income
and there is no job here.
Today we are going to discuss a lot about what is agency business and
Ajay ji who has been associated with ICC Lombard for a long
time is going to share all his
inputs with you.
Friends, it is very important to watch this video till the end
and please subscribe to my channel,
share it, comment and
definitely click the bell icon, only then
you will keep getting all the latest updates.
Your Jump Start
covers five unique diseases like
any member or ex-member has BP,
diabetes, asthma, obesity and
hyperlipidemia. If
any ex-member already has these five things, then this is an
optional benefit. By opting for this, they
can cover it from 31 days. Such features are
covered in 30 days for which no company is charging you
any extra loading after this.
You have chosen this option,
after this you will have to pay any extra loading and after 30 days
you are applicable for this thing. You
can make any claim here if you want.  Whether you want to
get a fresh policy or port it, both
options will be available here and there are many
inbuilt features which are also superior to the market.
If we see, if you
join us through Sir,
I will first tell you the advantage of joining through Sir,
if you join with Sir,
you will get support in every way, in every way.
If you go directly to ICS Lumbard,
you will get one RM, it is
not known how he will support you or not, but
Sir has his own office in Dwarka Mod, you
can visit him anytime, there is
no problem in calling Sir and the
advantage is that he also has a dedicated team, there are
four-five such dedicated team members
who will support you all the time. You have to talk
to the customer related to training, related to the product, and also get
them closed after talking to the customer. It means
you only have to learn here. If you
take the code here, learn means
you have started your business, you will get complete support so that
you can grow your business. We are
not sitting for ourselves, we are sitting for you, you will get
complete support.  You will get 110 rupees but I
just try to tell you this much that we do
all the recruitment digitally,
99.99% people join us from all over India
and right now the 200-250 people
who are already associated with us in Lord,
all of them are connected digitally, some from Assam, some
from Punjab, some from Maharashtra, some from UP, some from
Delhi, people from everywhere are associated with us
and no one faces any single
challenge because the company is running since 2001
and not from today, since 2001 it
is a digitally sound proof company, it
works brilliantly, their apps are so amazing,
their digital working is so
great that there is no need to go to any branch,
this is the power of Lord
and the company gives us complete digital support, it
aligns special training programs for our team, not only this, we
ourselves also remain aligned with our team,
where is the benefit for you, if you
miss any training then
we can give you the recording of our training,
you can watch
50000 1 lakh on YouTube  I can prepare a
complete road map for you on how you can start earning Rs. 10 lakhs
because we have so
much experience in this field. We have been
in this insurance for the last 27-28 years
and I have come into this profession by choice.
By profession I am a Chartered
Accountant, despite that I have been doing insurance full-fledged for the last
13-14 years and I am
doing insurance desperately, so you
can understand that this is my passion and my
passion is also that friends,
first of all you should leave your job
and earn more income than your job
in this business. Not 1 lakh, not 5 lakhs, not 10 lakhs, not even 1
crore, 2 crore crores can be
earned here. This power of the year can be
given to this business. This strength lies here.
If you manage to get only three or four customers a month, then
understand that your Rs. 40, 30, 0000 has
not gone anywhere. Only four customers, only four
customers can make you earn a year's working.  Suppose
you start having even 50 policies in a year, then
your kitty will start building.
At least our average policy is of ₹00. The
ticket size of an average policy is ₹00. If you do
50 policies, then you do business worth ₹1 lakh
in a year. If you work for 5 years, in
this way, your kitty of ₹50 lakh will be
ready. Even if you do not work from the sixth year,
15% of 50 lakh will come for
life. 75% of 50 lakh is 75 lakh.
And we have such agents who have
made a kitty of ₹10 crore, ₹1 crore comes to 1 crore, ₹5 crore comes to
15 lakh, ₹2 crore
comes to 30 lakh, ₹5 crore comes to 75
lakh and the one who has made a kitty of ₹10 crore earns
Rs. 1 crore annually, he keeps sitting and keeps
sitting and keeps sitting for life. This is the
power for which people choose health insurance
and in that industry
Renewal is at 15 which does
not come in any other segment, neither in life nor
in motor, this segment
can take you to the next level for life long, plus there are
some contests here, there is a
monthly contest, there is a quarterly contest,
plus we have some clubs,
Silver Club, Gold Club, Gold Plus, there are
different categories, based on the
business you do in the whole year, we also
give you a yearly trip, it will be domestic
or international and many times work will also
come with family, you
can qualify for two tickets, you can do three, you
can do four, this is only for you,
all the opportunity companies do for agents
and once an agent
joins Lombard, I assure you that
with this company, that attire, that
opportunity, all that
learning process is going to be life long,
you will always have to learn, you
think that once you learn it, it will be enough, no, there is a lot to learn, a lot to
learn, a
lot to earn
and Lombard in itself is  I
say it seriously, from my heart, there is
no challenge regarding claims in Lombard. Customer
satisfaction is tremendous. The
employees here, whoever you meet as RM, will provide you
extraordinary support, even
if you are at zero level and have
no understanding of any work at all. Dean works very hard to make you a hero from zero.
I have also been associated with Learn for the last
10-12 years, so I also make people
start from the same level and evolve in that way
so that your working goes to the
next level. And I will
try to explain only this much to you. You should
join Lombard as soon as possible. I have my
WhatsApp number 2. It will cost Rs. 000. After getting the code, it
is necessary to take a policy in the first month
with a premium of Rs. 000 and you will have to take 12 policies in a year, only
then your code will work. Otherwise, it will
not work. I am clear. I hope I am able to
explain it to everyone. You have to subscribe to this channel. If
you have
not subscribed yet, please please
subscribe. Thank you very much.
Thank you Ajay ji. Thank you.  You so much bye bye
take care
y